Draw your blades.
If we see it, it'll only be for a second.
Go!
It's fast!
In these trees, there's no way to
foresee and evade its attacks!
It'll catch us!
Captain, let's switch to Maneuver Gear!
Captain!
You won't escape!
Reinforcements from the rear!
Captain, your orders?!
Let's go for it!
It's dangerous...
We should kill it!
At this rate, it will catch up with us!
We kill it here...
That's why we came to this forest!
Right, Captain?
Captain, your orders!
Everyone, cover your ears.
Oh, my friend!
This is a victory for us!
Our fame starts here!
Oh, my friend!
Let us celebrate this victory for the next battle!
"I died for naught"
I won't let it end like that for you
until I am the last one standing
The enemy is cruel... We will kill...
The enemy is colossal... We will jump...
In our hands we hold blades of glory
and sing in the name of victory
We bear the wings of freedom on our backs
Swearing iron determination upon our hearts,
we slash apart the circle of idiocy
and soar through the sky
with our wings of freedom
Bite: The 57th Exterior Scouting Mission, Part 3
A noise grenade?
What is your job?
To just let yourself be swayed by whatever
you're feeling at the moment?
No, it's not.
Our squad's job
is to keep the brat from getting
a single scratch on him.
Even if it costs our lives.
It wasn't to keep watch on me?
We keep going on our horses, got it?
Roger!
Keep going? For how long?
And it's right on top of us...
Again!
The reinforcements!
If we don't help, they'll
be wiped out again!
Eren, eyes on the road!
Sir!
Keep your pace up...
Stay at top speed!
But, sir...
Why?!
If Squad Levi doesn't defeat it, who will?
Another one's dead...
And maybe we could've saved him!
One's still fighting...
We could still make it!
Eren, eyes back on the road! Keep going!
Are you telling me to look away?
To abandon my comrades and run?!
Yes, that's right!
Obey the Captain's orders!
I don't understand why
we're leaving them to die!
Or why he won't explain!
Why?!
That's because the Captain decided
the reason should not be explained.
You just don't understand
because you're still green!
If you get it, then shut up and obey!
No...
I can fight on my own.
Why am I relying on others?
I can just fight on my own.
What are you doing, Eren?
You're only allowed to do that
if your life is in danger.
You promised us!
Eren!
You aren't wrong.
If you want to, do it.
I can tell.
He's a real monster.
And it has nothing to do
with his Titan power.
No matter what power you
use to suppress him,
no matter what cage you put him in,
he will never submit to anyone.
I just want
to slaughter the Titans.
Eren, the difference between your
decision and ours is experience.
But you don't have to rely on that.
Choose.
Believe in yourself.
Or believe in the Survey Corps and me.
I don't know...
I never have.
I can believe in my own abilities
or the choices of companions I trust.
But no one ever knows how it will turn out.
So choose for yourself whichever
decision you'll regret least.
Eren!
Have faith!
I came up with a way
that'd only half-kill you.
Sir?
I said I'd only be able to stop
you as a Titan if I killed you.
But this method would only badly wound you.
Of course, it relies on the squad's skill.
The idea is to cut you right
out of the Titan's neck.
We'd end up cutting the ends
of your arms and legs off,
but they'd just grow
back like a lizard's...
Creepy, really.
Wait.
I don't know how they grow back.
Is there some other way...
So you're saying you don't want there
to be any danger or sacrifice?
N-No...
Then just resolve yourself.
We will, too...
The danger for us is
that you might kill us.
So don't worry.
Yes... Understood.
Th-Then, I can do experiments?
It's very risky.
But that doesn't mean that we
can't use him to investigate.
I can be in charge of planning this, right?
Eren, if there's something
you don't understand,
learn to understand it.
It's well worth any risk to our lives.
Ready, Eren?
When it's prepared, I'll use the
smoke round to notify you.
After that, any decisions are up to you.
Roger!
This dried-up well could hold
even a mindless Titan...
Probably!
That's the signal.
Since I sealed the wall, I haven't
tried to control the Titan.
If I lose control, Squad Levi
might kill me this time...
Did he not see the signal?
No...
His ability just isn't that reliable.
Hey, Eren! We're calling it quits for now.
Did something happen?
Hanji...
I can't become a Titan.
So your self-inflicted bite wounds on
your hands aren't healing, either?
No.
If you can't transform into a Titan,
our main goal of sealing
Wall Maria is off the table.
This is an order...
Make it happen.
Yes, sir.
Don't let it get you down, Eren.
But...
Well, it just means you're
more human than I thought.
Better than rushing into
something and getting killed.
This isn't meaningless.
Yeah...
We can't be too careful.
Why is everyone so calm?
Are they okay with my being
unable to turn into a Titan?
Are you okay?
Yes...
Hey...
What's that?
What was that explosion?
Why now?!
Calm down.
Captain Levi!
This is...
I said to calm down.
All of you.
What? What was that sound?
Eren...
What's the meaning of this?!
Sir?
Why now? Without permission?
Answer me!
Eldo, wait.
Answer him, Eren!
What are you thinking?
No, that can wait...
Prove you're not our
enemy, humanity's enemy!
Prove it! Now!
That is your responsibility!
I dare you to make a
single move with that arm!
I'll cut off your head!
I can do it... I'm serious!
Want to try me?
Oluo,
I said to calm down.
Captain, get away from Eren!
You're too close!
No, you're the ones who should get back.
Get back.
Why?!
My intuition.
What's wrong, Eren?
Say something!
Like I said...
No sudden movements!
Prove it to me, Eren!
I said I don't understand.
Answer us! You think we can't kill you?
I'm serious!
Do it now!
Are you even listening?
Okay, let's do this!
Are you humanity's...
Please shut up for a second!
Eren!
Can I touch that arm?!
It's okay, right? Right?
Just let me touch it!
Hanji...
Wait a second!
It's... hot!
Without the skin, it's really damned hot!
Unbelievably hot!
Squad Leader,
you're too reckless!
Hey, don't you feel it's hot, Eren?
How does it feel where
the right hand connects?
I really want to see!
That's right...
If I just pull out this hand...
Stupid thing!
Hey, Eren...
Don't do anything rash!
What?!
Wait, Eren... That was too fast!
I still wanted to
investigate some things...
Captain...
How do you feel?
Not... Not so good...
Until I saw that they were actually ready
to kill me, I didn't understand...
That they doubted me so much.
Of course they do.
That's why I chose them.
People say you only truly become a
full member of the Survey Corps
after making it back alive from a mission.
But whenever you fight the Titans,
you never have enough information.
There are too many situations you just
can't anticipate, no matter what.
They've had to cultivate the
ability to take quick action
and to make ruthless decisions by assuming
the worse case scenario.
But that doesn't mean
they've become heartless.
It's not like they felt nothing when
they turned their swords on you.
Captain Levi...
Squad Leader Hanji wants to see you.
Take a long crap?
Actually, it was pleasantly quick.
I wasn't sure what to tell the brass.
Well, for now...
Look at this.
A teaspoon?
Yes.
The right Titan hand Eren
created was holding this.
Like this, between its
index finger and thumb.
It's hard to imagine
that was an accident...
And for some reason,
the heat and pressure didn't
warp the spoon at all.
Anything come to mind?
I was trying to pick it up...
I transformed right after.
I see...
That may explain why you
couldn't transform earlier.
"Kill the Titans."
"Block the cannon shell."
"Lift the boulder."
In each case, you had a clear
goal before you transformed.
My theory is
that your self-inflicted injury
probably isn't the sole trigger.
You may need some goal, as well.
It's true that when I turned
into a Titan this time,
it was like when I blocked
that cannon shell.
But...
I turned into a Titan to pick up a spoon?
What the hell is this?
In other words, you didn't deliberately
change without permission?
No, sir.
Huh? Eh?
Wait, what are you doing?
That hurt...
This isn't easy.
I'm amazed you can bite through, Eren.
We made the wrong decision.
This is a small price to pay.
Not that it makes a difference.
Keeping you under control is our job.
And there's nothing wrong with that.
So don't get cocky!
I'm sorry, Eren...
We've been so jumpy.
You must be disappointed in our stupidity.
However, even so...
We're going to rely on you.
And we want you to rely on us.
So...
Have faith in us...
Eren!
You're taking too long! Decide!
I'll go forward!
Let me go!
I'm sorry!
Target is accelerating!
Go!
We will outrun it.
It's impossible to outrun it...
If we keep running away,
it'll stomp us all flat!
But...
We might all die,
but everyone chose to go on,
even if it meant abandoning our comrades.
Captain Levi has been looking
forward this whole time.
And the rest of the squad
believe in him, and put
all their trust in him.
I'll believe in them, too...
Like they
believed in me!
Fire!
Advance a bit farther, tether the horses,
and switch to Maneuver Gear.
You guys will be off on
your own for a while.
Eldo, lead the squad.
Once you're a good distance away
from the Titan, hide Eren.
Take my horse.
He can't intend
to take that Titan alive?
Well, Eren? See that?
We caught that Titan!
This is the power of the Survey Corps!
Don't underestimate us, fool.
Well? Do you get it now?
Yes!
Looks like it's stopped moving...
We can't lower our guard.
But you did well, leading it here.
Men in the rearguard squads died
buying us the time we needed.
We couldn't have done it without them.
Is that so?
It is.
Thanks to them, we'll be able
to see who's inside this thing.
I hope they haven't pissed themselves...
If we suppose that I am not me,
Can you say with certainty that you are you?
Will you be able to pick up after yourself
Once your sand-like shell breaks and your heart crumbles?
I could hear someone calling
But now my ears are just ringing
It's as if time has frozen
Now, wake up
I began to walk through a deep dark abyss
As swift as a gale, I escaped for my life
I felt like a living corpse
We break out of our walls
To reunite in worlds we've yet to map
Erwin Smith's secret plan was
to capture the Female Titan.
The aces of the Survey Corps try
to reveal its true identity, but...
Erwin Smith: The 57th Exterior Scouting Mission, Part 4
The aces of the Survey Corps try
to reveal its true identity, but...
Erwin Smith: The 57th Exterior Scouting Mission, Part 4